Just hang in there, Rohan.
I'm not gonna let you die.
Damn, I guess it picked up on my scent.
If those freaky-ass
phalanges catch up to me,
I can kiss my body's nutrients goodbye.
It can't travel faster than
60 kilometers per hour.
Lucky for me, this bike
can easily outpace it.
Problem is, I have no
clue how to find the user.
That foot fetish dick could be anywhere.
Alright, calm down.
Think about this logically.
Why would he lay a trap inside
a tunnel wall of all places?
You'd think ambushing us from the
side of the road would be easier.
Second,
there has to be more to this
nutrient feeding than meets the eye,
which means there's some
significance to the tunnel.
I've got no choice but to investigate.
I need to dig up some info
on that Futatsumori tunnel.
And I know just the man for the job.
I'll get Koichi and Reverb to
help me track down the user.
What's got you all riled
up, sweetie? It's okay.
Looks like I gave him the slip.
Now where's my card?
There you are.
You've got to be shitting me!
How'd it just appear out of thin air?
I was going 80 kilometers per hour.
Its top speed is only 60.
It should have gotten here
two minutes after I did.
That's simple math!
Though being a stand and all, I guess
it can pop in whenever it wants.
After it figures out your
rough location, it appears,
and uses scent to move in for the kill!
I gotta get out of here and fast!
S-60 kilometers!
Wait! What the? Shit!
It's a baby carrot!
If I decelerate, I'm a dead man.
And Rohan, too.
Slowing down isn't an option.
I'm just gonna have to gun it hard!
All right, Shining Diamond, do your thing!
And fix!
Nice!
At this weight, I'll never
get a chance to call Koichi!
Let's go.
Thank you.
We can party with us!
Just in the nick of time.
Lucky me.
You can consider that to me, so...
I must have a guardian angel.
Anyone there?
Damn it!
There goes a billion yen!
Shit!
Damn thing must have
broken when I grabbed it.
So much for a guardian angel. Fine!
If you hate me so much, just hang up!
What?
How could you say that, Minayo?
It's now or never.
Time to propose.
Minayo!
I love you more than anything!
Will you bet?
I take it back.
I guess it is my lucky day.
Man, do I have some great timing, or what?
Hello, Hirosei residence.
Koichi!
So that's the deal.
If I don't find the user,
I'm as good as dead.
I get the feeling he has an
obsession with the tunnel.
It's like he has a grudge
against it or something.
Any info on incidents
involving that tunnel?
There is.
It was published in
the paper two days ago.
I actually remember seeing
something about this on the news.
Some careless biker guy
was driving real drunk
and ended up crashing into
the tunnel's entrance.
According to this, he's unconscious
and covered head to toe in bruises.
He's in intensive care at
Burugaoka Hospital now.
Oh man, sounds like the stand got him too.
Is there anything else?
Give me a sec.
I remember the news reporting
there was blood all over the road.
You said the stand feeds by
absorbing people's nutrients, right?
The wounds are totally different.
Maybe the rider from the motorcycle
accident actually became the stand user.
If he's right, this guy's leeching
nutrients from others to heal himself.
Oh, shit!
It's the ocean!
Damn it!
I just can't catch a break today!
Gotta think faster, that water's
gonna mean some major shrinkage!
I can turn there!
Just have to keep it over
60 kilometers an hour!
Koichi, whatever you do,
stay on the line, understand?
All right, this is it!
Oh no, I'm totally about to fight it!
No, if anyone can make this turn,
it's Josuke Higashikata. Here I go!
Did you see that, you
fungal-footed asshole?
Clear that corner
without a single scratch!
What the actual hell?!
I'm charging straight
for the port of Mariah!
Let's go!
Shining Diamond!
Now fix that broken wall! Quick!
That was a close one.
It had me right in its crosshairs,
but now that the wall's up,
it's been totally blinded.
I guess that means this
thing finds its prey
like a mosquito sniffs out its next meal.
There's no rhyme or reason
to any of its attacks.
Its only objective is to
drain me of my nutrients.
That theory about this
being the drunk dude
from the accident is
starting to make sense.
It's all coming together.
Josuke!
Koichi, I worked it all out.
The guy from the accident
has to be the user.
You have to find out what his name is.
Got it.
Damn it, this is such a shitty situation.
I have no idea how I'm
going to get out of this.
Now where did that meddlesome
little shit Josuke go?
I have to admit,
when you selected that half-dead
biker punk as your next pincushion,
it caught me off guard.
I thought you were crazy, but
I see now how wrong I was.
You're absolutely astonishing.
Who would have thought that kid
would bring forth Highway Kick?
Stands are truly a
manifestation of the soul.
The hungrier they are, the better.
The insatiable hunger to
heal oneself is unstoppable,
especially when it comes to stands.
But oh, how nice it would have been
to witness Josuke bite the dust.
What do I do?
Come on!
Ditch!
Finding a disc that emptied into
the ocean was a lucky break.
But I still have no way to beat this
thing and it's closing in on me.
How the hell am I supposed
to make my escape?
So which way let's see the oceans behind
me and I need to steer way clear of the
water so going right isn't really an option
and I'm pretty sure I came from the left
which way do I go now I feel like the
ocean's to the left but what if it's
actually to the right there's also the
middle to think about what's happening?
I'm gunning it, but the stupid
bike is still slowing down!
C-could it be busted?
This doesn't make any sense!
The engine's working just fine!
So why won't the damn thing accelerate?
I'm grinding to a halt!
Crap! It's coming!
Wait a sec!
Am I out of gas?
Man, you had me freaking
out for a second there.
But I'm just in need of a little refill.
There's no need to sweat
over something so minor.
I was starting to worry
I had a major wreck on
my hands that even Shining
Diamond couldn't fix.
Nope, not gonna stress.
I can get out of this situation easy Pass.
I was freaking out over nothing.
A little tweak here.
And a little modification there.
It teleports though, so I guess
I can't get too comfortable.
At least I have fuel.
But if I'm being honest with myself,
I'm lost, which really sucks.
Where the hell am I?
And how do I get to
that freaking hospital?
Excuse me, I'm in a bit of a pickle here.
I need to know how to
find the guy from the
drunk driving accident
in Futatsu Mariah Tunnel,
and I need to know right now.
What's his room number?
It's an emergency!
Get off my case, kid.
And I suggest you read
that sign over there.
If you need your eyes examined, then you
can come back tomorrow morning at 9.30.
You don't understand.
I'm not here for a visit.
There's a reason.
I need to know his name.
I'm serious.
I need to know.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
I asked you to go home.
Pesky kids like you always
makes life hard for us adults,
and it really gets under my skin. Also,
you're pretty shrimpy for
someone who belongs to
a biker gang Do your feet
even reach the ground?
Do it act three.
Okay, master, let's kill the hoe.
Thank goodness that would
have been a disaster
These medications run
us 50,000 yen a bottle.
They're so heavy!
What the hell?
They're gonna fall!
Hey, you!
Don't just stand there
pitching and hold me up!
Sorry about that, Miss Adult.
Was that Hey You supposed
to be directed toward me?
Of course it was!
You're the only one here besides me!
I can't hold this much longer!
That sounds like a personal problem.
And you told me to go home, so I
shouldn't get involved, you know?
Besides, since I'm so shrimpy,
I probably couldn't reach it.
No, I do have a question for you.
Is your superior going to
reprimand you if those break?
I would do just about anything
to keep that from happening.
Fine, have it your way.
I'll tell you his room number.
Yu-Yupon Cameo is in room 525.
Just take that elevator up to
the fifth floor and you're there.
You can't miss it.
Josuke!
Koichi.
Koichi, did you find out where he is?
You need to head to the fifth floor.
His name's Yuya Fungami in room 525.
Thanks, you're the best, Koichi.
The stand, take the elevator.
Put an end to this Joe's game.
Damn, it's persistent.
Great!
Bastard's slipping his way in!
It's Koichi!
He's using Reverb Act Three!
I don't know what any of
us would do without you.
Thanks for having my back, Koichi.
Got him!
But Three Freeze can only
focus his attack one at a time!
The rest of those things
are going after Josuke!
There it is!
Room 525!
I can't believe I finally made it!
The fence!
Bastard!
I won't let you stop me when I'm so close!
I swear I'm gonna kick your ass
into oblivion even if it kills me!
There you are.
I hope you're ready, asshole.
Because when I make it to that bed, I'm
going to beat you within an inch of your...
Who the hell does this
douchebag think he is?
How dare you waltz into this
room without permission?
This is you's room, idiot.
Leave that loser alone.
You don't look so hot, pal.
I thought it had been a while since that
first guy in the tunnel
gave me his nutrients,
but now I know what
was holding up my meal.
So you're the second sap I've
been chasing around, huh?
Making it this far is commendable.
I'm kind of shocked actually.
Wait a minute.
You know who this guy is, you baby? Huh?
Not at all.
I've never seen the guy before.
Couldn't care less who he is.
Nice going, Highway Kick.
That's just what the doctor ordered.
Now, if I can just get a hold of
a few more suckers like this dude,
I'll be able to make a
full recovery in no time.
Get up!
Didn't you hear her, Buster?
Get your ass up and get out of here!
The question is, did you
hear me? Leave him alone!
Stop wasting your time with that guy and
give me some of that sweet, sweet loving.
You didn't forget about little
old hurting me, did you?
I need to take the piss of a lifetime,
and I'm not sure how much
longer I can hold it in.
Ooh, looks like it's time
for me to get to work!
What do you think you're doing?
We all agreed to take turns!
It's my turn to do it!
Hey, I haven't gotten to do it yet!
It doesn't matter who does it, ladies.
Just bring out that piss
bottle and give me a hand.
Okay!
Ugh, then I'll be over here. Huh?
Hey, Akemi! Hmm?
The peach you're holding has gone
bad, so use another one, okay, babe?
Sure, but how did you know it was rotten?
What do you mean?
I can smell that thing over here.
Any idiot could tell it was rotten.
You smelled it from there?
You know, you have a point.
My sense of smell must
have gotten better lately.
Hey, you're right. It's rotten!
If my nose is correct, one of
you beauties is on your period.
I'm right, aren't I? Who is it?
Um...
So it's you, Yoshi!
I hit the nail on the head and what's this
someone in here is
getting really pissed off?
When agitated the body
produces adrenaline and one of
you girls has discharged
quite the pungent secretion.
Are you the grumpy Gertrude Rock dear?
No, it's not me.
I'm as happy as a clam,
baby We're all just happy that you're
feeling like your old self again snow gums.
Yeah,
we've all been waiting for
this moment We couldn't be mad
if we wanted to right now
now now honeys tell the truth
Somebody in this room
is downright furious.
I can smell it loud and clear.
You better not be fibbing.
One of you is about to
pop, so tell me who it is.
It's me.
That full-bodied odor you're whiffing
is courtesy of yours truly, you dick?
That's bullshit!
Your body should be a
nutritional wasteland by now!
How in the hell are you standing?
It's simple.
You were sucking down my IV
like a malnourished vampire!
Calm down.
It was just a taste.
Even so it was enough to perk me up a bit
Rohan, you're holding him captive in
the tunnel, but that's about to end
You imbecilic numbnut.
It's like you've totally forgotten
that highway Kick has your scent
I don't want to hear a
peep out of you three
You can call me Josuke Higashikata, and
my stand is known as Shining Diamond.
I'm limited to close-range attacks,
but I can assure you my punching
speed is a lot faster than 60 kmh.
I've never measured, but if I'm close
enough, I'm sure I can get to about 300 kmh.
You just stay away from me!
I know by now you've heard that
my back has been broken to pieces!
My arms and legs are fractured, too!
I can't even roll over to scratch my ass!
Are you really gonna slap around a
feeble bedridden hospital patient?
All right, I admit it.
I was a jerk, but if you let me go,
I'll free the guy in the tunnel.
I think he's still alive, though.
It certainly wouldn't hurt
to give him some nutrients.
So do we have a deal or what?
Oh, come on, man.
You wouldn't beat up a
poor invalid, would you?
I know you're not that cowardly.
If you did, you couldn't
call yourself a man.
Yeah, so back off, you coward!
Damn, guess you got a point.
Beating the shit out of an injured victim
would leave a real bad taste in my mouth.
And it definitely wouldn't be manly.
It's not right, you know.
That's what I'm saying!
Kicking the ass of a tool like me
will haunt your conscience forever!
To prevent that nightmare, I've taken
the liberty of fixing you up. Hm?
Well, look at that.
You can move.
Congrats, you're completely healed.
Yeah, I'm totally fine.
Yup.
Since you've gotten a clean bill
of health from Shining Diamond,
when I pound your ass into the ground, I
can avoid looking like a coward, right?
Yuya Fugami's hospital stay, extended.
If you so much as think about
healing yourself with Highway Kick,
I'll just rearrange your
face all over again.
Insisted Josuke.
Man, I feel so invigorated.
I feel like it's the early
hours of New Year's Day.
And I just put on a fresh
pair of my favorite underwear.
You, baby!
However, being nursed back to health by
adoring fangirls isn't too shabby either.
As for Rohan...
Oh, it's you.
Guess you won.
So, uh, look, Rohan-sensei.
Here's the thing.
I know we're not friends, but...
Why the hell did you heal me?
You're such a moron.
I would have preferred wasting away
than have the likes of you save my life.
I told you to run away, but as always, you
had to step right into the enemy's trap.
How do you function?
By the way, you and I are even now.
And just when it seemed,
Rohan had come around.
On a different note, Koichi Hirose
decided to go on a walk with his dog.
Oh, it's a British Shorthair.
Where did you come from,
you little sweetie?
A little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you,
but ooh, I gotta find you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you,
but ooh, I gotta find you.
Raquel!